<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Hospitality: Room Service</name>
  <author>ledronas</author>
  <packageId>ledronas.hospitalityroomservice</packageId>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.0.0</modVersion>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>
Adds guest services on top of Hospitality.

MEDICAL TREATMENT
Guest beds can be flagged medical again (Hospitality normally disables this). Colonist doctors will tend injured visitors, who pay for treatment in silver - or get treated for free if they can't afford it, so nobody dies over a bill.

COMPANIONSHIP
Designate a colonist's own double bed for entertaining guests via a new bed toggle. Colonists with the new "Companionship" work type enabled (off by default - opt in per pawn on the Work tab) may invite a visiting guest back to their room. Success is based on the colonist's Social skill and Beauty, respects RimWorld's normal gender/orientation compatibility, and hands off entirely to the game's own lovin' job - nothing explicit is added or depicted. Guests pay for the privilege once the encounter actually finishes.

On top of the base mechanic:
- Trains Social skill, one of the hardest stats to raise normally.
- Pawns slowly grow more comfortable with the work over repeated sessions (mood + success chance), with distinct trait reactions for Prude/Asexual (dislike it) and Insatiable, if those traits are present (Vanilla Traits Expanded compatible).
- Slaves react differently: a consistent negative thought each time, and their Will (escape/rebellion chance) is worn down - though if fully broken down while still growing strangely used to it, even Unwavering Loyal can eventually crack.
- The bed's sheets visibly tint burgundy while the toggle is on.
- Soft integration with "Intimacy - Friends n' Lovers", if installed - a completed session also feeds its Intimacy need.

MEAL DELIVERY
Companions may also bring a hungry guest a meal right to their room instead of making them go find their own food, for a small delivery fee - the room service theme, extended to meals.

SLAVE COMPANIONSHIP TRAINING
A slave can be individually marked for companionship training from their Slave tab. Once marked, they're a valid target for the Companionship service the same way a visiting guest is - no silver changes hands, but a successful session trains their Social skill and boosts their suppression instead.

Every price, weight, and chance above is a slider in the mod settings, and each major feature has its own on/off switch.

Requires Hospitality and Harmony (load after both).
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>Orion.Hospitality</packageId>
      <displayName>Hospitality</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/753498552</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Orion.Hospitality</li>
    <!-- Optional - "Intimacy - Friends n' Lovers", soft integration only, not required -->
    <li>LovelyDovey.Sex.WithEuterpe</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
